<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UX on Seb's Blog</title><link>https://sebastienray.github.io/tags/ux/</link><description>Recent content in UX on Seb's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 13:46:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sebastienray.github.io/tags/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Robots Replace Designers</title><link>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/willrobotsreplacedesigners/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 13:46:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/willrobotsreplacedesigners/</guid><description>Algorithm-driven design tools can help us to construct a UI, prepare graphic assets and content, and personalize the user experience but can they replace us?
While I was browsing trough the &amp;ldquo;2021 UI/UX Design Trends and How To Make Them Work For You&amp;rdquo; article by Kate Shokurova which I recommend you take a look at. At the end of chapter &amp;ldquo;#2 AI and other tools to the rescue&amp;rdquo; the authoress talks about the usage of AI in UX/UI.</description></item><item><title>Field testing Niseko website</title><link>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/eyetracking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 12:36:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/eyetracking/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently discovered a website &amp;ldquo;realeye.io&amp;rdquo; able to do eye tracking using only the webcam. It was during a course named UXLab, and we learned how to do an UX interview using exe tracking and how to analyse the results. That day I went back thinking how I could apply the new knowledge to my activity with Niseko(my agency). Most of our clients are small PME and don&amp;rsquo;t have budgets allowing crazy UX field testing.</description></item><item><title>3D Transforms in Adobe XD</title><link>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/xd-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 17:46:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sebastienray.github.io/posts/xd-update/</guid><description>Adobe XD just had an update and I needed to know what was up ASAP. So I went on youtube to Howard Pinsky&amp;rsquo;s channel where I always fin everything about XD.
In my agency we mostly use Adobe XD to show the web design to the client before starting to code. And clients are more and more demanding nowadays. The feature around 2:40 and 3:50 will be useful to show off in future meetings.</description></item></channel></rss>